[
    {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "The TCP header specifies which value to ensure that data is processed by the correct application?",
        "answer": "Port"
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "Which TCP flag is used to gracefully terminate a session between two systems?",
        "answer": "FIN"
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "Which statement correctly characterizes the functions of the OSI Model? It is a...",
        "answer": "method of describing the functions of a networking system to allow communication"
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "Which common services occur at the presentation layer of the OSI Model?",
        "answer": "Encryption and Compression"
    },
    {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "The physical address applied by the data link layer of the OSI Model has which features?",
        "answer": "It is expressed using a 12-character hexadecimal value and it is unique to every network interface"
    },
    {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "Which device or service would not operate at the physical layer of the OSI Model?",
        "answer": "IP Address"
    },
    {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "Which type of communication would be analogous to a half duplex transmission?",
        "answer": "two people using walkie-talkies"
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "question": "A fixed payload typically has which benefits or characteristics?",
        "answer": "they can be more efficient than variable payloads and they are always the same size"
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "question": "If you needed to be certain that your data transmissions are being received, which type of connection and protocol should be used?",
        "answer": "Connection-oriented and TCP"
    },
    {
        "id": 10,
        "question": "Which command can be used to determine the MTU optimal size?",
        "answer": "Ping"
    },
    {
        "id": 11,
        "question": "Which protocols operate at the application layer of the OSI Model?",
        "answer": "SMTP and HTTP"
    },
    {
        "id": 12,
        "question": "Which type of traffic management service occurs at the network layer of the OSI Model?",
        "answer": "Routing"
    },
    {
        "id": 13,
        "question": "Which device or service would not operate at the physical layer of the OSI Model?",
        "answer": "IP Address"
    },
    {
        "id": 14,
        "question": "The physical address applied by the data link layer of the OSI Model has which features?",
        "answer": "A"
    },
    {
        "id": 15,
        "question": "Which layer of the OSI model is responsible for node-to-node data delivery and framing?",
        "answer": "data link layer"
    },
    {
        "id": 16,
        "question": "Which device or service operates at the data link layer to manage node-to-node communication?",
        "answer": "switch"
    },
    {
        "id": 17,
        "question": "What is the purpose of the Logical Link Control (LLC) sub-layer in the Data Link Layer?",
        "answer": "b"
    },
    {
        "id": 18,
        "question": "What is a key distinction of the components at the physical layer of the OSI model?",
        "answer": "b"
    },
    {
        "id": 19,
        "question": "Which of the following is NOT a responsibility of the Data Link Layer?",
        "answer": "d"
    },
    {
        "id": 20,
        "question": "In the OSI model, which layer is responsible for transforming data from bits into electrical signals for transmission?",
        "answer": "physical layer"
    },
    {
        "id": 21,
        "question": "What is the primary purpose of the Media Access Control (MAC) sub-layer in the Data Link Layer?",
        "answer": "Handles physical addressing, specifically using the MAC address of devices, and helps establish direct node-to-node communication on the same network."
    },
    {
        "id": 22,
        "question": "Why is the layered approach of the OSI model beneficial for network communication?",
        "answer": "allows for effective communication by organizing network functions; ensures vendors focus on the entire network protocol stack; divides data communication into seven layers, each with a specific job, making it easier to isolate and troubleshoot issues"
    }
]